A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Virgnia Secretary of Administration, 1972 - 1985 (Bulk 1984-1985)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1972-1985., Extent: 23 cu. ft. (23 boxes). (Box 1-23)
  - House Document 5 - Commission of Status of Women: State Personnel Directors Listing, 1982-1984. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - House Document 5 - Commission of Status of Women: Telephone Survey - Training and Development Opportunities for Women, 1982-1984. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - House Document 5 - Commission of Status of Women: Training and Mobility, 1982-1984. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - House Document 5 - Commission of Status of Women: State Training Director's Listing, 1982-1984. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - House Document 5 - Commission of Status of Women: Governor's Fellow, 1985. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - House Document 5 - Commission of Status of Women: Each State Listed (Women's Training Survey), 1982-1984. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: ABC - Metropolitan Cash Register, 1982-1984. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Commission for the Arts, 1982-1984. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Attorney General, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Capitol Police, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Commerce and Resources Agencies - General Correspondence, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Comptroller - Moving and Relocation Regulations, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Comptroller - Directives, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Comptroller - Directives, Financial Statements, 1982. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Comptroller - Directives, Recievables, 1982. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Comptroller - Directives, Compliance, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Comptroller - General Accepted Accounting Principles, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Comptroller - Internal Revenue Service, Meal Reimbursement Ruling, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Department of Corrections - General, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Department of Corrections - Parole Board, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: State Office of Emergency Services, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Game and Inland Fisheries, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Human Resources Agencies - General, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Health Department, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Highways and Transportation, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Highways and Transportation - Aircraft Realignment, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Industrial Development, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Internal Auditor, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Internal Auditor - Agencies Internal Activity Program, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Virginia State Library, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Virginia State Library - Records Disposal, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Local Government Advisory Council, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Military Affairs, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Mines, Mineral, and Energy, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Office of Minority Business Enterprise, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Office of Minority Business Enterprise - Business Procurement Goals, Reports, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Planning and Budget, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Planning and Budget - Directives, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Port Authority, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Social Services, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: State Police, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Supreme Court, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Transportation and Public Safety - General Correspondence, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Virginia Executive Institute, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Water Control Board, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Governor's Office, 1982-1984. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Governor's Office - Correspondence, 1984. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Governor's Office - Correspondence, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Governor Dendy, H. Benson - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Agencies Other than Administration: Governor ETV Broadcast, 1982. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Education: Agencies - General, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Education: Armed Forces Tuition Rates - Budget, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Education: Educational Computing Subcommittee, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Education: Higher Education - General, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Education: Decentralization Proposal from College Presidents, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Education: Higher Education Decentralization Task Force, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Education: Executive Agreements - Background Information, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Education: Exemption Requests, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Education: State Council of Higher Education, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Education: South Eastern University Research Association, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Education: Department of Information Technology Base Data, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Education: Higher Education Employment Reports, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Colleges and Universities: General, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Colleges and Universities: Community Colleges - Virginia, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Colleges and Universities: George Mason University, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Colleges and Universities: Old Dominion University, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Colleges and Universities: Virginia Commonwealth University - Medical College of Virginia, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Colleges and Universities: William and Mary, 1972-1985. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - A-95 Review System, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Process Act, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Aerobic Exercise Class, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Agency Publications, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Aircraft, State Owned, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverages in State-Owned Buildings, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports - Publications Questionaire, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - ASPA, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Biographical Sketches - Cabinet and Agency Heads, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Block Grants, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Budget: Amendments, 1985. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1986-1988. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Budget: Fiscal Outlook, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Budget: Bipartisan Appeal, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Budget: Federal, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Monuments: State Owned, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Monuments: Commonwealth Building - Roanoke, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Monuments: General, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Buildings and Monuments: Finance Building, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Buildings and Monuments: Historic Landmarks, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Buildings and Monuments: James Monroe Building, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Buildings and Monuments: Ninth and Franklin, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Buildings and Monuments: Old City Hall, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Buildings and Monuments: Supreme Court Building, 1972-1985. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Capital Outlay: Finance Building - Capitol Square, 1981. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Capital Outlay: Study - The Finance Building Capitol Square, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Caiptal Outlay: 14th Street Twin Towers Project - Phase 1 and 2, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Center for Governmental Affairs, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Center for Innovative Technology, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Central Agency Controls and Procedures, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Central Garage, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Chambers of Commerce - Richmond and Virginia, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Employment of Chaplins, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Charitable Contributions: Payroll Deductions, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Old Planter's National Bank Building, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Concurrent Jurisdiction, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Conflict of Interest - General, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Use of Consultants: General, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Use of Consultants: Agency Reports, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Contracting for Services, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Dale City Branch Office, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Downtown Development Unlimited, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Early Retirement Program, 1972-1985. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Electronic Funds Transfer, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Employment Levels - Executive, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Employee Suggestion Program, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Affirmative Action, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: General, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Complaints - Inquiries, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Conference - Blacksburg, Va., 1984 Oct. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity: Committee, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Equipment Financing, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Executive Decision Support System, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Executive Orders: Robb - General, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Executive Orders: Robb - Number 1, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Executive Orders: Robb - Number 47, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Executive Orders: Robb - Numbers 2 and 6 (Moratoriums on Hiring), 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Executive Orders: Dalton, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Executive Orders: Holton, Godwin, Tuck, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Executive Orders: 1978 and Earlier - General, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Federal Government - General, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Federal Priorities, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Fiscal and Accounting Classification Study, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Fixed Price Contracts, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Flag - Procedures for Flying, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Future Commission, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Green Spring Property, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Hay Associates Study, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Hay Associates Study: Department Participation, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Health Care: General, 1972-1985. (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Health Care: Recommendations and Procurement, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - James River Corridor Study, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Summer Job, 1984. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - State Mapping Program, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - March of Dimes Walk-America, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Model General Assembly, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - National Governor's Association: Winter Meeting, 1985 Feb 24. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - National Governor's Association: General, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Organization Membership Reports - Agencies, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Organizational Charts - State, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Parking: State Parking Deck, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Pay for Performance: Booklets, 1972-1985. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Performance Evaluations: Commerce and Resources, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Performance Evaluations: General, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Performance Evaluations: Salary Information, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Performance Evaluations: Educations, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Performance Evaluations: Finance, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Performance Evaluations: Human Resources, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Performance Evaluations: Transportation and Public Safety, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Advisory Commission, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Prompt Payment Act: General, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Prompt Payment Act: Secretary of Transportation, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Puplic Meeting Facilities - State Use of, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Publications: State Agencies Annual/Biennial Reports, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Study, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Regulatory Review Process, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Retrocession: Blue Ridge Parkway, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Retrocession: Fort Norfolk, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Richmond Renaissance, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Salaries: College Presidents, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Salaries: Correctional Officers, 1972-1985. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Salaries: Deputies and Employees of Circut Courts, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Salaries: Faculty, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Salaries: Probation and Parole Officers, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Salaries: Salary Survey - General, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Salaries: Salary Survey, 1983. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Salaries: Report to Governor and General Assembly, 1982. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Savings Bonds Campaigns, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Section on Budgeting and Financial Management Task Force, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Section on Budgeting and Financial Management Task Force: Curriculum Reform, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - State Employee Assistance Project, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Southern Governor's Association, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board - Executive Program, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Science and Technology Task Force, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Set-Off Debt Collection, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Severance Pay for Gubernatorial Appointees, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Southwestern State Hospital: Actual Working Figures, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Southwestern State Hospital: Actual Working Papers, 1972-1985. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Southwestern State Hospital: Study Correspondence House Joint Resolution 83 and 283, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Southwestern State Hospital: Study Correspondence House Joint Resolution 83 and 283, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Standards of Conduct, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - State Fair, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Sturman, Ron, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Suggestion Award Letters, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Teleco Study, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association/ College Retirement Equities Fund, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - State Travel Contract, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - United Leasing, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - United Way Campaign, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - User Charges - Fees, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Vehicle Usage Study, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Wage Employment Study, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - YMCA/John Tyler Community College Land Proposal, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Executive Tracking Reort, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: General Bill Information, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Budget Information for Legislative Leadership, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: LGM's and Proposals, 1985. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: General Session Information, 1985. (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Comparable Worth Study - House Joint Resolution 35, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Early Retirement, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: Fragmented Military Leave, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: Standard Nomenclature, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Legislation: Studies Requested by 1984 Session, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Legislation: Veterans' Preference Bill, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Legislation: House Joint Resolution 147 Studies, 1972-1985. (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - General Assembly: Delegate Correspondence, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly: Senator Correspondence, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly: Willey, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly: House Appropriations Committee, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly: Senate Finance Committee, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - United States Government: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - United States Government: Represenatives Correspondence, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - United States Government: Senators Correspondence, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - United States Government: Trible, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - United States Government: Warner, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - United States Government: Wolf, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Applications to Wayne Anderson, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Joint Legislative Auditing Review Committee Documents and Working Papers, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Joint Legislative Auditing Review Committee Documents and Working Papers: Study of Secretarial System, 1978. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Joint Legislative Auditing Review Committee Documents and Working Papers: Camp Pendleton Study - House Joint Resolution 14, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Joint Legislative Auditing Review Committee Documents and Working Papers: Follow-Up Studies, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Joint Legislative Auditing Review Committee Documents and Working Papers: General, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Joint Legislative Auditing Review Committee Documents and Working Papers: Aircraft - Use of State-Owned, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Joint Legislative Auditing Review Committee Documents and Working Papers: Cabinet Reorganization, 1972-1985. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - House Documents: Realignment - General, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 1 - Secretarial System, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 2 - Realign Secretariats, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 15 - Transfer CDB, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 16 - Transfer Grievance Procedure, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 17 - Merge MASD/DCS/Telecommunications, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 18 - Economic Development, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 19 - Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 20 - Conservation and Historic Resources, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 21 - Marine Products, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 22 - State Educational Assistance Authority, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 23 - Auxiliary and Block Grants, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 25 - Medical Assistance Services, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 27 - Registration of Radio Shippers, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 28 - Aviation, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - House Documents: Recommendation 29 - Parole Board, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - House Documents: House Bill 816 - Deferred Compensation, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - House Documents: Senate Bill 342 - Merge Schools for the Deaf and Blind, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - House Documents: Realignments, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - House Documents: Department of Medical Assistance Services, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - House Documents: Virginia Supplemental Insurance System, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - House Documents: Peat, Morwicky, Mitchell and Comapny Report, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Governor's Office: Judy Griswold, 1972-1985. (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Governor's Office: Dendy Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Governor's Office: Correspondence, 1982. (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Governor's Office: Editors Luncheon - Summer, 1983. (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Infant Mortality: Southern Regional Task Force, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Infant Mortality: Press Invitations - Tidewater and Richmond, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Southern Regional Task Force - Infant Mortality, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Infant Mortality: Briefing Papers, News Articles and Policy Position, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Infant Mortality: Prevention, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Infant Mortality: Children's Defense Fund and General, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Infant Mortality: The Virginia Perinatal Association, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Infant Mortality: Childrens Hospital Lunch, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Infant Mortality: Task Force - Atlanta, Ga., 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Infant Mortality: Miscellaneous, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Infant Mortality: Resource Mothers, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Infant Mortality: Responses to "I Didn't Mean to Hurt You, Baby" - Fetal Alcohol Syndrome, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Infant Mortality, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Infant Mortality: Reception, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Infant Mortality: Miscellaneous, 1972-1985. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Jobs for America's Graduates, 1972-1985. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Jobs for Virginia's Graduates, 1972-1985. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Jobs for Virginia's Graduates, 1972-1985. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Jobs for Virginia's Graduates - Contributions, 1972-1985. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Jobs for America's Graduates, Inc., 1985. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Southern Regional Task Force on Infant Mortality, 1985. (Box 23, Folder 6)